<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE pkgmetadata SYSTEM "http://www.gentoo.org/dtd/metadata.dtd">
<pkgmetadata>
	<maintainer>
		<name>loong0</name>
		<email>longlene@gmail.com</email>
	</maintainer>
	<longdescription>
		Overview

		Libevhtp was created as a replacement API for Libevent's current HTTP API. The reality of libevent's http interface is that it was created as a JIT server, meaning the developer never thought of it being used for creating a full-fledged HTTP service. Infact I am under the impression that the libevent http API was designed almost as an example of what you can do with libevent. It's not Apache in a box, but more and more developers are attempting to use it as so.
		Libevent's HTTP pitfalls

		It was not designed to be a fully functional HTTP server.
		The code is messy, abstractions are almost non-existent, and feature-creep has made long-term maintainability very hard.
		The parsing code is slow and requires data to be buffered before a full parse can be completed. This results in extranious memory usage and lots of string comparison functions.
		There is no method for a user to access various parts of the request processing cycle. For example if the "Content-Length" header has a value of 50000, your callback is not executed until all 50000 bytes have been read.
		Setting callback URI's do exact matches; meaning if you set a callback for "/foo/", requests for "/foo/bar/" are ignored.
		Creating an HTTPS server is hard, it requires a bunch of work to be done on the underlying bufferevents.
		As far as I know, streaming data back to a client is hard, if not impossible without messing with underlying bufferevents.
		It's confusing to work with, this is probably due to the lack of proper documentation.

		Libevhtp attempts to address these problems along with a wide variety of cool mechanisms allowing a developer to have complete control over your server operations. This is not to say the API cannot be used in a very simplistic manner - a developer can easily create a backwards compatible version of libevent's HTTP server to libevhtp.
	</longdescription>
</pkgmetadata>
